You didn't raise your voice, you didn't raise your hand Just stood there quiet like you didn't understand but I saw your eyes
Just this hour at the table
Just whatever's true to say
I built a council.
leaking just the truth and what you do with that i'm i'm i'm the miss
The daughter needs a song, the family needs a 330
It's true
I guess, uh, I guess the show's over. I mean, it's like, Jamie, it's just you and me.
I mean, if people can't even like, hang out for like, introduction, I don't know.
And that's really behavior or something. Wow.
Like not, oh, not one person. I mean, just you and me, Jamie. Just you and me tonight.
Well, it's okay, it's supposed to be you and me.
Let me see, oh, maybe like, I don't know, let me see.
I think I can guess the, oh, I have a little bit of burger left.
I guess, let me get my mouse.
Where's my mousey, mousey poo?
I know, where'd everyone go?
Like, everyone's given up on me, I guess, except for you.
I do appreciate that.
do appreciate that well hi guys I don't know I don't think I've ever had I mean I
think I even had like a bit larger and I larger chats when I first started on
if I guess to go shadow band or something I don't know I did unlike
private like all my videos today like all of them like everything
So there's a whole library, so I guess maybe everyone's just watching other shows or something. Hi Rudy
Hi, Rudy. Well, no one comes. I don't know
Guess I don't have that much stuff prepared working on some stuff. Oh my gosh
Oh my gosh, did it work? I failed? Oh, failed to plug it home. It's like, I don't know, it's shit
Huh
Well, it's okay. It's like, you know
Maybe I'll start going to tick-tock instead
It's gotten a little bit like ugly here, you know, it's like
And I'm Rudy's meowin
I'm Rudy
Tux was an art get tux was inside earlier
It's good. Well, I'm happy. It's just you and me. Hey, it's better than a
Yeah, a hundred trolls one friend, you know
Better than a hundred trolls
I don't know. I bet it's like I really don't know like I got what people hate me so much. It's like
Basically, I just tried to like I tried to like be nice to everybody like everybody
All right, that's it.
Like I get, I guess it's like,
I guess like trying to please everybody,
please there's nobody or something like that
because it's like really nobody's coming in,
like not even like coming in.
It's like, be the end Jamie.
Well, oh well, ghost was here earlier.
Or maybe it's, I don't know, it's 11, 20, you know.
I don't know. I mean, I think it's like small because I did see like even blogger has like he's at 60 people
He has like 15 people and so maybe everyone's over there
Maybe there was over me. I have already was wrong. Oh
Oh, what do you mean? Oh, yeah, he had some bacon tonight. You had some bacon. I
Thought we had a good show last night though, but Kate didn't say like she was like
Oh my god, um, they're talking about bestiality and everyone's like, oh my god, they're so disgusting or he's and I don't know. I don't know.
I guess, um, everyone's over it.
Hmm.
It's okay.
It's okay. Hi.
Hi, what's wrong? What's up?
Yeah, he loves bacon, you know.
Mr. Root, he loves some bacon.
Fuck, and I mean, I don't have,
I just have some to tobacco
and like a little bit of a cheeseburger.
I actually have a little bit of a copy and.
Actually, I thought, I thought,
it's kind of ironic because I thought like those songs were
like some of my best songs.
Like I think, I think.
And then it's like, people, I saw people,
one of the people came in, but they all left.
They, it goes like two and then I'll go back to one.
Like they're just checking in to see like,
oh, is he crashing out?
No.
And they'll leave in a second, probably.
They're not saying anything.
Hi, babe.
Well, you know how many hours I have of like,
I was looking at it like when my studio,
I had like 35,000 hours.
It's like I need like 2,000 for months. I'm so like over the qualified for Monza station, but it's like I can't apply for a while
so
Yeah, yeah
Like today, I guess Brandon's like there, you know
There's like the other chat like crystal. I guess crystal lands like the new sensation. Like, you know, she should like 60 people in her chat
just trying to troll Brandon and then it's like I don't know I think that a lot of them are for
people from here you know and it's like now it's like I uh but I'd rather be friends with like
him than any of them really
I don't care if he's controversial
And if it's like and sometimes yeah, sometimes if you stand your ground on things or and you just do what you think is right
It's like it will be not popular, you know
it'll be
quite unpopular and I
Oh, hey, Joanie. How are you? Yeah, it's a little bit quiet in here. I mean, it's just like it's just been
Here for like how long like 21 minutes. It's just been Jamie and I like no one's no one's come out
coming tonight, but um
Still, yeah, I just said, you know, I slept all day. I don't know what's really going on right now, but yeah
Okay, we're some people trickling in
Everyone shout out. Hi. How are you doing guys?
Yeah, I
Had a nice a good nap and good sleep today. Oh, do I have alcohol?
Drinking less is more right. Yeah, you're like just hanging out with us. We can have just have a
it'd be like there's like some people watching not talking though what are they doing there's
spying on us well that's okay so yeah I can't see bacon oh Rudy was like Rudy ate the whole piece
of bacon you know oh he has glass where's my glass yeah I got it right
got my champagne my champagne
Cheers guys, look at they left
I
Think probably goes went to sleep goes goes with oh, so goes some call me or I don't know if he wants me to tell the story
but he he actually got attacks
because he was talking to this lady and
He that gave us heard his number backstage or whatever. I hope I can tell the story and then
It turns out she might be a little bit slow or something like that.
So now people are calling him like a PDF because
she's not, she's like, you know, she's in her 20s or 30s or something like that,
but because she's slow, they're saying he's like some kind of,
but you know, who stuck up for him this summer and Christine
were like the only ones to come to his like assistance.
I mean, he was really depressed about it. It's kind of sad.
I just think people are just like, so
So overreact of these days about every like little thing. It's like, I don't know
It's like my ghost is a
This is a very simple nice person, you know, it's like he's
He actually is starting his own channel like and I really want him to get to his 50 subscribers and stuff
But it's like almost like I almost like
When I'm almost like I don't know if it's good for people to come and do YouTube anymore. It's like first of all
YouTube is like being just a dick right now with the monetization and stuff that they're taking away monetization from a lot of people
From huge creators people with hundred thousand subscribers and things like that or over because you know if they if they ever use a voiceover
That was an AI voiceover or anything like that, right?
They they take away the monetization. So they've just been demonetizing everybody and I and they had me do like a video appeal and
I did, you know, I spent all this time like you know sending up the camera and the preparing
What I was gonna say and like, you know doing and showing exactly like, you know, how I make my stuff and
I submitted it and they're like, oh two it will take two weeks to for an answer or whatever
And then it was like the next day or that night. What up what would I eat today? I had a I had a
Cinnamon bagel, you know, it was pretty good old videos. Yeah, there's a lot of old people older videos and stuff like yeah
But they didn't even watch nobody even watched the video my video appeal like no one watched it has zero point zero
Like knowing it no one from YouTube looked at it not even looked at it
It was just like no one viewed it
It's just like they just have computers figure doing everything and then you say you you can't really do anything about it like
And plus, oh, here's up here's I just really it's really annoying. That's like I'm I did write on Twitter
That's one of the things you can do is I kind of reach out there and they kind of like sometimes will
Will have someone look into it for you, but you know, I'm not getting my hopes up this time. It's like
But I take away I take off a lot a lot of content
But I did but most my content like 90 99% of it is just open panels and totally original stuff and like
Thousand thousands of hours. So there's Ilya Ilya. Where are you today? You and are you in Germany today? How are you in?
Duisland, are you in Netherlands? Are you in?
Yeah
Hey, oh, that was a nice bro. Oh, hey, Riz. What's up? How are you doing? Yeah? Well, I am I'm having it. I'm having a this is a
Doesn't look like a classy drink. It's like kind of fluorescent pink or red. It's uh,
yeah, um, I was also trying to make it. I tried to make a really cool like, um,
like video about something and then it's like, and it made it too small, too short and
hold on to it. No, no, no, it's longer now. Hold on. Let me see. Let me see how long it is.
Video. Okay. Oh, the video is much short. Yeah. It seems that there's an issue generating
That length and better approach would be to create the video in smaller parts. Okay, I don't know
It just came out two minutes long when it's supposed to come out of ten minutes long
Do they like they like?
Okay, I don't know
Anyway, the software is like kind of now now it's trying to charge more and it's just a hey, what's up guys?
Yep, so how are we how is the weekend? You know
By the way, it is almost midnight. So or I think you know, you're in Berlin. Should you go outside?
Okay, you'll join in 10 minutes. That sounds good. You know, everyone enjoyed that just just the three of us. So so
But uh, just the three of us
It's okay, it's okay
You know
It's like really there's so many people that are I'm glad are not here anymore because they're not like they weren't really true
fans true friends, I mean I wish I would have
kind of
Made more more people and stuff, but I like you know liked me, but
Yeah, we can make it if we try yeah, just the three of us
Yeah, it's kind of a little bit a little bit sad. I don't know
It might be because
Strokov told that that story about the dog and stuff like that it was the kind of like just to me
It was kind of comedic and like you know, I just have a weird sense of humor like but it's like they were they were saying
Oh my god, he's so sick
just for hosting that stroke off person and
It's like Kate was doing today, and then everyone was like, oh my God, we can't even listen to it.
And even that NorCal who was telling the story about literally how he stole women's panties,
and they were like, I don't know where everyone is. I don't think, I don't know.
But yeah, he was telling a story.
Like, first of all, I was telling a story about what Bita told.
Bita told a story about her grandmother when she was a little girl.
Her grandmother said that no sex before marriage except the back flaps or something she said.
She said, not the front flap, the back flaps.
And then people got all mad about that.
I was like, I'm just telling the story, beat it.
No one got mad when she said everyone laughed.
Maybe I just said I pulled it wrong or something like that
or it's offensive when I tell it.
I thought it was a kind of funny story.
I don't think her grandmother was serious.
Maybe she was.
But then stroke up to the story by the dog,
giving him a rim job accidentally
when he was having sex and I thought it was kind of funny.
There's four, yeah, and it's been 20, 30 minutes.
I know there's five watching, wow.
Well, I know too, and it's like,
then there's like all these people in Crystal Anne's chat
or I guess that's the new popular place to be.
I don't know if she's on.
I haven't seen anybody really on tonight.
But it's okay, it's okay.
I didn't, you know, but I'm saying like YouTube is like
really just pissing me off anyway.
They're being really unfair.
You know for someone like, you know, it's like I've invested so much money and like most of the money
I made on YouTube I've invested back into the show and then just to have it and then oh, you know
Here's the worst thing is that they'll say okay. Well, you're kind of like, you know, you know
in our inner an original content or whatever and so
Okay, and so then demonetize and then
But they don't tell you what it was or what like what exactly it was, you know, there's because it's just a robot that
They basically use an AI
They made they use an AI and then the AI demonetizes people and some people got a lot worse than I did really
Because some people like you know make a lot more and and
and are losing their channels.
There's a lot of people that are super talented,
like there's this guy, I think he's in touch or something,
and he makes this dragging cartoons,
and he started out just doing them by hand,
but then he's like, whoa, I figured out,
I could do this AI rendering,
and I could do things that I could never do before,
and then he was demonetized.
He was an old, little old man, and stuff like that,
and he was just like, yeah.
Yeah, hopefully yeah, hopefully you can um
Believe that you can do that. Yeah, that'd be awesome. Okay, so
I don't know is there something wrong with the
Jamie I think Jamie needs to check her um did you it's um a request and I think it's gonna be in the
It just looks like a little thing on top.
I think on the very top, there's a little should be look,
a little red notification.
Yeah.
But I'm saying, Jamie's like bad at technology.
I remember, I remember, I taught Jamie how to cut and paste.
Right?
So, yeah, just have a look.
And,
it's good.
Like I said, my dad used to,
He had a ledger. He had like a little book that he would do all his all his math and all his calculations
And he he was a little calculator and that's all he used he never used a computer his whole life
But he wanted us to learn how to use it
But he was like he just didn't like he didn't like cell phones though. He liked he liked to learn how to use a cell phone
I mean like how do you he likes a cell phone? He wasn't the latest cell phone
He really know how to use it. I always have to explain how to do certain things on it for him. Oh, there you go
Okay, okay
Yeah, we're good. Okay, there we go. Yeah, this is Lola. Rudy's back there.
Lodor, come over here. Hey, Lodor. Oh, I have my pie. Yeah, I'd like to use my little...
Oh my gosh. I think it's... I think that's my pie's time of the month, you know.
I'm so bad. Yeah. Lola likes me. I like being my laugh.
Yep. You're my little babe.
Yep. My little guard cat. All right.
Hey, baby.
Yeah, you know I used to, in Glendale we had ravens and ravens do a, they make a little sound like
They make a clucking sound. They don't go
That's what crows do. Ravens do a
Make a little clucking sound
It's a very, oh my god, there are so many around my area
I don't know if I attract ravens or something. Well, I did but now there's parrots here
We have these little, I used to have a parrot like them. They're called conures
and they're green with like little red heads,
with red heads and stuff.
And I had one named Lucy
and she was actually named Lucifer, right?
Lola's confused because Tux came home.
Yeah, he was just in here and they love each other, you know,
but he stays for a little bit, he sleeps and then,
and then he kind of like, you know,
he kind of, Rudy kind of scares them
and because Rudy's new.
Yeah, run him back in here. I don't know where he goes, but he I saw last night. He has his he has his testicles still
He's got his full testicles and
Um, they're black because he's a black cat and it's so fun.
Like yeah, he's deep on home and then I was going, I go through like, you know, the next
door every day.
Like that's really like going to be more effective than actually like going around the neighborhood
looking because it's like the cat's not, it tricks with anywhere and walking distance
up here.
He would have found found home.
Right.
People expected me to be walking around like like and stuff like that.
Yeah, he does.
But so it's like better so I just go in next door and then it's like there's so many cats
But it's like and I keep thinking I'm gonna see tricks somewhere in there
But I and I've looked every day, but I don't see them and so hey money for 20. How are you?
I don't know where everyone is tonight. It seems I don't know either. Maybe a shadow band. I don't know
There might be like a there might be some flagging campaigns or something
Yeah, it could be 30 40 miles away, right? It's like, you know and
They can hear like, I mean, they can literally hear like a cat like me out from like five miles away
And so they'll go like a long way away and maybe sometimes they get lost and stuff
Good to see money for 20. Yeah, but I know it's like a lot of people are it is a holiday tomorrow and
You know
But we had interesting night last night and I am alone a little bit earlier. I remember on 11 usually on like a one in the morning
A lot of people are sleeping.
Oh, you're so comfortable, huh?
Tastes?
No?
Okay.
I don't know, bakelives?
Could be.
There are...
A lot of people that hate me right now are it's like I was just like RG came back last night
actually RG was here last night. Did it go good and not particularly?
He was kind of rude. People who are on a strike war channels are getting much struck one after
another. I know there is a strike war going on too guys. There's like a bunch of channels
are going down like money you haven't unmonitized you I did too. You know it's like it's not
our fault, you know, it's, it's, it's like, it's just some kind of
like YouTube, but here's the worst part. YouTube is still like, they'll say,
okay, well, you have an original content or whatever, but, and then we're not
going to pay you anymore. But then they'll, they'll put commercials on our
channels. And so they'll get paid for, for our content.
And so what's that about?
It's like, it's just, it just seems like really unfair.
You're a monetized, you got a bunch of videos set
to age restriction, you got a strike.
Yeah. I mean, it's like, and it's, I don't know.
You know who I blame?
I kind of blame that Harry Tatzika's person.
I don't want to like, you know, it is bullshit.
It's really, it is bullshit.
It's like seriously crazy.
I wish there was like another.
I mean there are other platforms but they're not like that great, you know
It's like I mean they don't this is like one but it's like like there's so many people is like if you notice
There's so many channels getting demonetized right now because they have this like AI
Yeah, where do you do already?
You're like looking over here. Hi
You say hi, maybe five
I'm pet you okay
You can't decide, yeah, what are you doing, Root?
I don't know.
But yeah, so I'm probably gonna make a,
I might put, I mean, I can apply in a couple months.
So I'm probably gonna move any of my,
I'll probably move my music videos to a separate channel.
I'll just have the live streams on this one.
Maybe that will be better, because then I like, yeah.
But it's just like a big pain in the butt.
Plus it's like once you do, it's like then it's still a thing.
Now I'm just gonna be, oh, can I post my letter post this?
Is this too, I mean, cause there are people that like,
really like, like people that use it at all, like anything.
Like they do, they do voiceovers with it.
If they do like animation with it,
it's like there's so many channels.
Like they'll say, oh, you know, he's not hungry, he's good.
You hungry?
I got all food, I got food out.
Hi, babe. Link the pen? Okay. I'll link the pen. Can you hand me your pen, please?
I was kidding.
Interrogation trauma. Hey, Leah, how are you?
Interrogation trauma? What does that mean? You got interrogated.
There you go.
Look at our look at him.
You're just sniffing around and
Yeah, okay, let me look at how my this content is doing. Do you have anything interesting to show you?
It's a gem. Oh my god. Okay. Well, did it it picks it? Hold on. Oh
My gosh
Okay here, let me see how much how much do they add to it?
They hardly anything. Okay. Bizarre. Okay. I didn't pin the link either. I've been working on some
software on some stuff. Okay. I'm going to pin the link. Here we go. Okay. There's a link. Give it a spin.
Oh my God, it says it drafted the hook segment.
How long is 600 seconds?
Oh, it says 30 seconds.
Why did it say 30 seconds?
Oh, that's why I did it.
It was on 600 seconds.
It was supposed to be like 600 seconds and now it's 30.
Okay
It's like but I do like use this thing for video clips and it's like
That it's basically free
And it's like it creates the best video clips because there's services that charge so much
that like I
Hardly give you anything. I was able to generate just a few clips from them. I mean they were nicer clips, but
Like kind of better animation, but okay
You have a super interesting video, okay, let me see what is going to come out, okay?
Here we go
I should do baseball baseball, I don't like baseball cards though
Work super picky
Hi
Maybe that's why let's go
No, isn't that like some kind of tears thing don't I mean come on
Thank you. I'm not Sam and I don't like Yu-Gi-Oh cards.
No. No baseball cards, no Yu-Gi-Oh. How terrible.
Where are you? Germany?
I know I am.
You're mean to
They still oh, yeah wall. This is Germany. It's German. You'll come in
Hey, Sweden Freud
What is the other laws?
Guten tag oh
My god
My god, you have a goat. Oh my god. Oh, it's my god. Okay. Hey, what does that say but what bots?
Yeah, I need some I need some money to hire dingbots dingbots. What is a dingbots like a dingbats? Dino
Dino like dinosaurs
You're fucking Americans. You are so fucking slow. I know I know but it's a dinosaur
posters with dinosaurs
What is that advertising, what a museum, what's going on, I don't understand.
Yeah, they just cloned dinosaurs in China, and now they are in Germany.
I'm lying, this is not Jurassic Park, okay?
Well, I mean it's like doesn't look very so you are yeah, so you know you have to see the Jurassic Park movie
From the night before or something. Yeah, so you know dinosaurs
Everyone's thought everyone knows what a dinosaur
I don't even believe in dinosaurs
They probably take a bunch of bones from a bunch of other animals and put them together to make it look like some kind of
Dragon or something. I don't know
What do you think that's my theory
Oh, my opinion, of course, I would say that the CIA made them CIA. Yeah, I would agree
Now I know why my nobody no one's at the show anymore. I think the government is
Hiding my channel
Oh my god, okay. Oh, yeah, or your channel is too gay. Yes, you gay
Yeah
For me, it's not gay enough, but everyone else is too gay
What's what's your bit? What's your most favorite gay experience you've had going to like a?
What gay experience
If somebody's nice to me, that's a good gay experience. This one being nice to you. It's not gay
But hey, uh, anyways, this is called the tenney land
can you hear me?
Tanning lamp?
Can you not yell and see the microphone?
It's a little bit loud in my ears, okay?
Am I?
I'm sorry.
It's a little bit loud, yeah.
It sounds a little bit loud.
Okay.
I tried to calm down.
Okay, you tried to calm down.
Are you on a lot of stimulants?
No, I'm having this.
Headphones, so I don't know where the mic should be. You said who beat up their mom's s. J. Who's SJP?
I live SJP. Oh, who's SHP? Who's ship?
Where's that Samper? I don't know. Oh, Joe Shipley. Oh, Joe Shipley beat up his mother. No, I
Don't think so. He wouldn't do that. I don't know his mother was
Who is he's gay, so he wouldn't do that
Or some shit. He's not interested about pussy. They said some subhuman pull-off. That sounds like a racist
Oh that pico gram. Hey pico gram
Yeah, oh, I think you are projecting yourself
If you say stuff like that
I don't know you mean but okay. Hey, look at it. Look at your shadow
Living in the shadow
You heard that song he's from oh, he's from Denmark. Yeah
Well, he's not a he's not a pollock. That's I mean, I think pole on pollocks are from Poland
Sir um, what is it? I don't understand what anybody's saying. I'm so sorry
Okay
So, okay, so which language is this? Okay, if somebody's wondering where I'm not
Mother's up with Montauk
Benny Montauk be some stock
It is called even war bees
I don't want to see gas one thing war
That I mean, it's a really good place. I don't want to look at like it's like a store
I mean, I want to look at some landmarks and stuff. This is this is so boring. Come on. You're the worst tour guide ever
I just came out of my fucking a hotel
Literally showed us a poster of a dinosaur and then a gas station window. I mean, I'm gonna go find something more interesting, please
It's not a gas station. It's called any mark. It's a mini mark. Okay. Yeah, big difference
Okay, I want to see like a castle or something. Oh, I'm sorry. You are having your periods today. I'm sorry. It's a morning
It's morning here. Everything is closed. It's Sunday
Well, it's I mean first London. Do you understand that I know but you're supposed to be more excited
At least I can say oh my god. Well, this is this, you know, you're not really teaching us anything. Whoa, that's a big cock
Where where's a big clock? Okay, this is where I'm at
It's called the girls first
It's his cult culture house the cult house. I'm a cult house
That would I think culture house? What does that mean?
Culture house a cult house of culture. Yeah, yeah house of culture in a English
So you speak English, right? Yeah, but we're repeating in trash everywhere
Looks it was terrible. Where's the graffiti answer crash? Oh, you see the walls that are covered in that paint. Oh
Here oh here is the everywhere. I mean, it's like I've literally everywhere
Where is it a German people want to look cool they want to look cool, but they don't it looks terrible
I mean, it's like it's ruining the country. Hey, we have over a double digital jack. It's 10 people. Wow
Look at this guys. Wow. We're going through a dark alley. Okay. I think this is where Ilya gets his blow jobs in the middle of the night
right
from a guy
We were you knocking on where who's whose door is that? Are you stealing mail?
Well, I'm my neighbors your neighbors. I do live here. That's my neighbor you're on vacation
You live here
On the YouTube no, I don't know I mean
Who's that my it's my
Yellows oh my good god. Oh, huh. There's somebody in there guys. It might be a drug addict in there
It buys everything just abandoned this is gonna be depressing
Hold on
Here there we go here
I'm gonna watch from the side
So, okay, so we what are you just an abandoned building? What is this?
Where are you? Oh?
This is Sunday in Europe
In the morning, and there's but why are there any people? I mean it's like it's like you're going through like a dark
Like it looks like scaffolding or something like that. What the frick?
Oh, yeah
What is this?
Deutschland I haven't seen one human being yet
Really, okay. I have you but there's no there's none
There's not here. Yeah, everybody. I like what's going on. I mean, I think I did you did okay
I'm sorry. It's okay. But don't tell that to FBI
Well, the FBI doesn't have jurisdiction in Germany. I don't think do they?
Okay, don't tell that to CIA.
Do they have jurisdiction in Germany?
I think they do.
Okay, okay.
What do you mean, the A-S-I?
We all sing I, right?
Not the CIA.
Okay. Well, okay. Well, Ilya, I mean, it's like, come on, is there anything interesting
here in the shows? Or, I mean, this is not like a sleep stream. I'm not trying to bore
everyone to death. I mean, can you, can you like, but you are going to sleep. So I think
it's a good, you know, you go knock on that door of that mansion right there for the Rothschilds
home. Is that where the Rothschilds live in there? Is there an eyes wide shut party we
Masquerade Bowl
Okay, I mean is there I don't is there the train stop coming here years ago. I mean is they what is there?
I mean I
Don't know what I don't want to do with this guys. I think I think I think you I think you chased away like my whole audience
I'm gonna blame you from now on
for your for these for these tours of
deserted train stations, I mean
Can you go knock on a door at least and then say hello?
Can I have a give it a great coupon? I don't know what I don't know what's going on. What's that building over there?
I mean
Grasping at straws with you
Hello
Can you call out for signs of life?
i don't think there's anybody in there anybody out there
good god can you lay on the train tracks for just for like fun
maybe a train will win oh yeah it's a good content yeah should i go there yeah just lay
just laying out on the train tracks i bring for the train oh that's all mean i'm just kidding i'm
just kidding how are you oh i didn't know that
I thought you were serious that I should go there and kill myself.
Yeah, oh my god.
Hey, can I see your Casio watch?
That's kind of interesting.
I've never seen a watch.
Did you get that watch in 1980s?
No, it's a Timex.
It's Timex.
Oh my gosh.
But yeah, it's a beautiful green digital face with a brown...
It's a huge...
Yeah, oh my god.
But an ugly watch.
I've never seen an uglier watch than that.
Why did you get that watch?
Well, it's America. No, why would you buy that like do you like even like, you know
Yeah, well, you know watch on team who that looks at least at least uh, at least a little bit, you know
Bansier, I mean, it's like how much did that watch cost five dollars?
That's a $5 too much. Yeah, I know it did come out of a
Machine you put a penny in a penny slot machine. Hi. It won't be save. What's up? Okay now now we're filling up
I don't know. I think Ilya has
I think I think he I think he
Chlorophyll my chat or chloro not chlorophyll chloroform you chloroform the chat
I know we've been wandering around aimlessly through Germany for the past week. I mean, we've really not seen anything
I'm gonna see if not except for the Nazis. Okay, capitalism's look
But what's happened here? This was so sad
Camp in where fur is that anti fur?
What is where fur like is fur like a fur?
Unsure zoom can yeah, we fight for our future
They are they are like a communists. Well, where are they? Oh my god, the communists took over this place. Oh my god
Oh, yeah, yeah, they are so is that way everyone and they will kill every every homosexual like you
So be aware it will what I mean. I wouldn't doubt it
completely satanic
Know Pico. I met Pico Graham actually in Benny's chat like probably two and a half years ago
So Pico and I go way back remember Pico. We went to the the the comic book convention while we watched that together
Remember that Pico a homosexual. I don't think so because he's he's mean to me and it's like and I've known him for years
And he's like he's he talks shit like right in my face. He's terrible
No, that's so mean
Well, remember when you mooned the show and then you peed in a bucket on the show and I almost got
No, they banned because of you now you've taken my audience
I think that was like a five years ago. It wasn't five years. It was just last I've been on for five years
It was last year
They literally like maybe like less than a year ago
Remember that when you were the kills and then you kept trying to pull it up. I mean we didn't have undue underwear on
Don't remember that. Yeah, that's how you were killed. You don't have a underwear. Okay. Well, some people do
Oh, that does is verboten
Does is verboten in the in Deutschland?
Verboten means forbidden
You know, you can you can change the f's for the V's it's kind of interesting f and V make a similar sound
Yeah, that's right. Yeah, I don't know. He doesn't speak English very well. He doesn't
Really, where were you born? No, we're not the English speaking here. No, I'm a vision. Do it's
Entschuldigung
Yeah, only German is spoken. Yeah, I know I know don't leave don't please don't leave guys
I know it's boring, but it's like, you know, it will get better. Maybe we'll find
You see that guys, here we go guys everyone
The board hold on hold on guys
Yeah, um, so this is what happens when the country loses the war, right?
So are you as is Berlin or West Berlin or they don't make it a distinction anymore. I
Think this is the post the coast
Can't go to the ocean or something
post
East voice who's that who's that with that voice? I was I heard a guy's voice. Who's that?
Can you go talk to the conductor?
Are you getting on the train?
Yeah, this is a
special train to Auschwitz. They send me to Auschwitz. Please. Oh, stop it. Please do something. I don't care
I mean, I gotta be better than this place. I mean, come on
Is there anybody in the train you can talk to perhaps look around
You're you're alone in the train in the middle of no, I mean, it's like crazy. It's not that funny
Well, so is it there's a rent cheap where there's like absolutely nobody even living
Like I didn't like seriously. I haven't seen one human being besides, you know, you and your dumb watch
Oh, there's a person go talk to them
Hi, you're on you're on YouTube live on YouTube guys
You ask you some questions. Oh
You have to say something more naughty
You have to be more mean
That's your job. They are used to homosexuals and bun sex. Well, then they'll love you, right?
Hello
I mean, is there anybody, but you're not even talking to anybody, you can be mean to somebody,
I don't care, be mean, be nice, just talk to somebody.
I'm talking with you.
I don't want to talk.
I'm talking with you and I'm listening to you.
Talk to somebody else, I don't have anything to say right now, I'm in a bad mood.
You are talking all the time, you fucking bitch.
Oh, did you say it to me?
That you are absolutely right. Oh, I hear that way that you were speaking German
Yeah, it was German and to leave it like a more crap. Are you going to the tourist area? Oh
Like a butt block or a gay club tour. No, I'm not their butt plug plays around. I mean, it's like that's
Can you plug your butt?
No
What did that voice say?
It said that you have a loose butthole.
I have a police on you.
Oh, that's my train to Auschwitz. It sounds like that.
Hey, that's on the board is very fucking clever. I like a summoner
Oh, I hope he's not
Yeah, are you Jewish?
Oh, I have my foreskin I can show it to you right now if you want
No, I have a foreskin. No, put it away. Put it away.
It's here. It's here. I don't want to see it. No. No. I don't want to see your buddy.
Oh, these pants are American. Can you see these pants, this brand? This is American. Whoa.
he's done it with his shoes look like oh yeah they're 10 years old riding with the style
where do you shop like the you know the german thrift store
the the do you do you find your clothes in a bin by the side of the the road
what is this all the most no no no no just put your penis away please i don't want to look at it
okay well so where are we going tell us about where we're going oh i don't know nowhere you
don't know or somewhere you're just you've got it where do you want to go where do you want to
go what do you want to hear let me go anywhere please so we're not here not here i don't want to
Mean it's to place with people
Okay, that's enough. Okay, that's enough. I mean, I can't take it anymore. Go away
Come back when you found something interesting. I mean, I'm sorry guys
Try my best. I
mean, wow
Imagine that's your tour guide
No, he literally I have not see I saw like one person sitting in the train. That's it
I don't I've never seen anything like this. I
Think that's he pays like a dollar in rent because he has a whole city to himself. I mean
He's still there
Hey, okay next station next station I'm leaving
Okay, okay
Okay, okay, um pack yourself up. Let me see if this is a channel
There's a new channel called pack. Oh, I think it's called pack yo self like why oh watch pretty good clip on the last night
You should have gone insane a pack me is it pack yourself up. Let me pack
Yeah, so
Okay, I found it has a picture of beat as a witch that's pretty good. Okay, so let's see
Let's watch a clip here. Do you want to see blogger show of his ear juice? Oh, I don't want to see that
Vicky and Matt's okay
It's this Barry's channel has buried the turtle versus Victoria J. Okay, let's
Tell me James shows his foot. I mean why is this all it's on the literally channels all foot pictures and in Barry
Sounded good
Yeah, let's watch something. Okay. I'll come back later. Okay, extra one. Well, we'll come back later. Okay. We'll see
Oh, there's a person. Okay. I don't get here anymore. Okay. I'll come back later. Okay, okay
Well, let's watch some of this looks like kind of this can be interesting. Let me see
Um, it's called Glass Houses, okay?
Oh, Broom Gang. Yeah, Broom Gang is a lot.
Sam and...
You know, he's exactly the kind of person that I'm talking about where they're like,
they feel overly entitled to the attention of women because they've got a porn, retard porn line complex.
Like, they jerk off to porn so much that they're like, oh yeah, this is,
this is the kind of woman that I deserve to talk to and be around.
And then they have like this fake complex in their mind that they're actually good enough to fuck porn stars.
And then, they start talking to women that would never even talk to them or fuck them in real life.
And they think that they're entitled to talk to them.
I know.
They should talk to them too. Which is wild.
Hey, there's seven people.
If a woman wouldn't fuck you in real life and you're going to shit talk her,
you look like the clown.
I'm sorry.
You are mad because she wouldn't fuck you.
That's it.
You're mad because she wouldn't fuck you.
And everybody around you does that shit.
And it's so obvious and pathetic that it's really weird.
What is this?
These are like the fucking dumb fucks on the playground that couldn't be nice to girls.
They had to bully them because they were never taught proper behavior.
What the fuck is this?
Girls over that they want to actually be with because they're fucking
done little cavemen retards and they've never grown up from them.
They don't know how to be nice or anything like them.
They have to be assholes, and that's their fucking game
in their M.M. It's so weird.
What is this?
Exactly, but when you're a wet brain,
you don't have any self-esteem.
If you're literally on your everyday fucking drunk,
you have nobody better quality in your life.
It's PicoGram.
It looks like you people.
The same.
If you had a high quality fucking man or woman
behind the scenes, you would not be putting all of your time
and attention into this.
I don't want to have sex with anybody.
I don't like putting your time and attention into.
The person you're with want to come in it come in it. Yeah
And the interesting part is that he dated KK and they live close enough to drive
Shit, what the fuck is that?
Is there a monkey talking oh my god, it's a whole time is a monkey talking the fuck is that I mean
Let's try this one. I don't know
Fair use that is you and Matt Silver hate bonding spreading fake news about big thug
Barry the turtle on a phone. Oh, bro. Barry. What are you doing in my chair? Where is it?
He's right there. Just keep him here, dude. Just so everybody what's his name? Uh?
Pack yourself up
Oh, that's a cliff channel. Yeah, and that's Barry. That's Barry right there. Oh, he was promoting his own clip channel then because he was promoting himself.
Barry, you're a deadbeat fucking loser. Why don't you go take care of your fucking kids? You're too busy taking money from a single mother and literally taking the food as someone else's kids mouth.
You can even put food in your own.
Shut the fuck up. Go make some more AI art to make yourself look all fucking special, bro
You literally are a fucking pathetic Victoria J. I think that there's a reason why no bitches fuck with you
There's a reason why you only have the the blowfish by your fucking side, bro
Who's the blowfish?
I know that she was called big Ben. This is new. Okay
What kind of fucking hustle bro? You mean being a deadbeat fucking unemployed loser?
that leeches off a mentally unstable woman? Is that something that we're promoting here?
Uh-oh. Promoting somebody who can't take the basic thing?
That's a troll. That's a troll. Take it as how it is.
Is that really her back? It's a fucking cage chat dude. Well, she's gonna handle her you know women children
revenge porn's them makes fun of
elderly deceased mothers and the boo-hoo's and cries about Sam and calling her a fat bitch
We find the way you are one. So oh my god, Victoria
Oh way back
Ugly motherfucker, Barry, Barry.
Barry, Barry, you're nobody to talk about anybody's looks.
Come on, old man.
Is it cringesaurus?
No, sir, you look like a crack head that I use.
I think it's a toilet, Jay.
You know, holding up that foil to your fucking mouth, bro.
Did you hear Lisa anybody dude you some fucking like crusty ass old man
Please don't kick anybody
Dusty dusty that Kate that Katie bait or Kathy Bates can't give you fucking lotion for your fucking nasty skin
Oh my god, you're at your ass. She needs there. Yeah, she needs
can't save your ass she's skin but you know what can lotion you should use it
it's your friend I like also you need to get a fucking job and support your
family stop taking food out of other people's kids mouth it's fucking sad
pathetic you're not a fucking man
What are you fucking talking about bro dude? You don't have a girlfriend. You got nothing
Barry all you have is your right hand for your three inch
You got like are you like the heart? I thought it was a can of beer
paying you for all you got you know in your fucking life bro like you know dodging child
support taking money from an unhinged woman having revenge for being ugly as far baby do me a favor
no woman would what is this gay guy talking jigglypuff baby like put in your paypal link
because i don't want to leave my phone at all yeah put it in it let's do it real quick push down
Yeah, it's like very dude. You are an ugly motherfucker, dude. I wouldn't even let my shadow touch you. That's how fucking
Busted you are next. Hey, baby. That's great. We can like next string. My shadow
Gets more action than you fucking ever did your whole entire life
Yes, it's me Maya
Next screen, we can like show some interesting pictures of all the ugly busted people
Exactly
You don't know the definition of docks the shit that you've done to be there
Graduated from school hard knocks. No, this is back to that and we talk more about buttholes
with no fucking job.
Bear, you about to run?
You about to run?
You going scared?
Yeah, it's going to go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Wait, are you going to, are you going to cry to Kate?
Are you going to cry to Kate?
I'm going to ask Kate to give you some more money.
Hey Alex.
To buy you some fucking good lotion.
You fucking need it.
Bear, if you really need it, I will send you $10
so you can get some lotion for your ashy,
like me that the ashy folks,
I will help you out and send you $10
so you can get some lotion on the ashy.
Yeah, dude too bad you can't do anything about your fucking ugly ass face. Oh my god. Ugly motherfucker talking about plastic surgery, but I'm not sending him that much.
No dude, he needs more than that. That bitch, that motherfucker. I think it's an inhaler. The ugliest thing that I've ever seen. Bro, you've been talking about me.
You're both so much alike except she actually has money you don't oh
That's the biggest difference. It's the cums you latch on to her you fucking parasite. Yeah victory is hellin
That's best. Okay. Hang on. I'm gonna do you don't have to add
Sam and bro
Like the whole thing and like our thing and what we wanted to talk about okay, and don't let him yell and over talk
Don't someone couple off
I know, I don't care, I don't like Jacob Silva, I don't like him, I don't like his place.
Why you like put chains on me?
Oh my God, not Sandman.
That's no racism, Sandman.
She didn't get a racial way.
You better put rules on me.
Stop that.
How long you gonna say live, how long you gonna say live, Vicky?
You're not long dude, I probably like you.
Can you tell her real quick like why was Tripp trying to like dish you and
little bro you and disrespect you, she doesn't she doesn't know what happened.
So you can explain your own words, what happened?
You think you think I'm gonna have on.
I don't care about it, I just want you to explain.
He's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, he's like,
What does that what? No, no, I'm Matt and I donated to KK. I donated to what other
Steve you want to go there? That's boring. So like why waste our time you donate to big T2
No, I didn't, all your exes, all your exes, but peps, I don't, I don't know how much money
you gave her.
So let's focus off of that, because that's just gonna be a loop and go nowhere for you
and focus on what you want to talk about.
Would you like that little dweeb?
Oh my God.
Dude, how about a little dweeb at 6'2"?
Okay, why are we even having these stupid conversations, I feel like I'm in high school
right now.
Why are we doing a dick measuring contest?
Come on, man.
We're not the barrio.
I'll be back, yo, I'll be back.
I don't, I've never even heard of this person.
Okay, bye.
Oh my.
I'm just taking your temperature.
You acted different with me.
I'm happy of my temperature, dude.
I'm just, you're the one coming on here, saying.
She's acting different with me.
That's my woman.
She's how she was told to act different with me.
I'll be back.
Stay live, though.
We'll be here for the-
We'll be here, dude.
That's just clearly human nature.
That's what people do.
I'm six-foot-three.
With people that they are in alliances with
that have-
Yeah, no lying.
Pack yourself up, Barry.
There's a little lesson for you.
We'll come in and say that shit.
and go pay your child's poor boy what so anyways what's going on are you watching
this fucking stupid bullshit
why did you time them out let the little bitch speak dude like um he was fucking around about
your paypal and donation so he needed a time out for that oh oh yeah it's barry you're a fucking
he's trying to take money out of your mouth he's trying to like make him kind of take it the food
out of Kate uh Kathy Bates's kids mouth that is a lot of food that you're taking if you take it out
of her mouth and you take it out of her children's mouth dude that's they both they both look like
What dude, what are you talking like honestly? I'm a berry dude. Go fucking pay your child support, bro
Go do that
Or you just one of those dead beats that are not even on your kids birth certificates
Is that is that coming you you're reaching so hard on this woman
Do you owe so many fucking you know money to the government for child support that you can't get a steady fucking job?
Because you're gonna you know cut your check in half
No, you got your bitch to do that for you get her to do that like she does everything else for you
Dude, that's all you do you latch on her fucking ass is pathetic, bro
You're not a fucking man any man that abandons their children and can't even fucking provide for them are scum
You are scum of the earth
And I feel sorry for you the baby mama that you ejaculated your nasty ass into that poor woman is stuck
To take care of your kids and provide for them while you can't how does it feel to know that your children are being raised by?
another man and not you
Busted ass fucking crust. What does he do?
Disgusting
You are
You all you are Barry you go on fucking panels you make threat threats to women on here
You collect dossiers of nudes and let me explain something to you. Okay, so you can understand. I know you're stupid as fuck
but you're not allowed to have any type of news.
I don't care if you found it on a fucking stream yard.
I don't care if you found it on Discord
and it was a public server and the person posted it there.
If you do not have permission of those news,
you can get in trouble.
It's called circumvision, you dumb motherfucker.
Oh my God.
It cuffs on you for that shit.
You're dumb, you're stupid.
You are worse than a doctor.
You're a revenge porn fucking freak.
And you would go into federal prison for that shit, you know, if you released people's
like addresses on your yeah, you could get in trouble for that.
But is that the equivalent of fucking releasing the news that you do not have the permission
of the person in those photos.
No it's not, bro.
The FBI can go and literally get your fucking ass on that shit.
You can get charges for that.
You could go to fucking jail.
I think I've had enough of this shit.
Fucking ass.
you worried about me and my fucking shadow i don't want to be here anymore i don't want to be on
this subhuman fucking scumbag it's harassing women on here and using their revenge porn over
their fucking heads but yeah no i'm a bad person because i i made like an uncomfortable laugh
you want you don't want the drama no i don't like drama i mean the cops on me i'm bored
You didn't cook shit bitch you cook anything. I think you cook was your fucking sad pathetic ass by
Creep or what why the fuck I'm listening to this fucking whore hey
Well next screen I will have some can we watch something else
Oh my god.
Oh spasiiba. Spasiiba Balssar.
I'm gonna leave you in charge of the show. Do you not porn bomb?
Are you lacking in psyche?
This is how people live on the streets of Europe.
They have these RVs. Small ones.
Amerikāni norvīs jau bija,
And here it says,
Herzlich Willkommen!
Well, Herzlich means like heartenly.
Can you even say that in English?
Oh.
Well, anyways, heartenly welcome.
Because heart, heart means like heart.
So, so, well, you are welcome.
And that's actually a term in a wanking glove.
That's how you usually use when you go to park and you masturbate.
So that's how it is.
Ja tämä on oikeastaan Eurooppaan vähä.
Se on se, miten me olemme tyhjeltäneet olemme,
olemme olemme, kun on vähä.
Psyki, oletko vielä siellä tai mitä?
Can you hear me, man?
What else are you?
Joe you're playing a song. No, if you're playing a song I apologize. I don't want to join right
I'm so fucking tired. I'm so fucking tired of joining like or not even joining but like seeing other people's streams
And just like the gayest fucking like the bleh bleh bleh like thank God I could join a real man's podcast. Thank you
I mean, I don't know. I think like
Make stroke optimal syrup at a dog butthole last night. Now all hell's broken loose. I mean
Exactly like Jesus Christ leave the dogs alone. Like leave the dogs
Your orange hairs freak this guy has orange cuba cares
So what am I raising back your Roni's Roni's? I'm waiting for a check to cash if you can hold your little ass
Afternoon, I got you all the McDonald's you are in the world
At this time you're gonna be fucking who I made the McDonald's my boy
When was the last time you fuckers left your houses?
Hey Alex, Alex, when was the last time you went out?
You stay at fucking home like this gay simple.
I stay at home like this.
You fucking faggot, you don't even go outside.
I don't even go out.
Fuck you man.
You have to go across the planet.
You definitely know my you are afraid to go out
You're afraid to go outside
You're good. He literally walks around Germany and nobody gave a
This guy's a bomb bro. This is a crackhead in Germany. This is a crackhead in Germany. That's what he's showing us
We're not the only crack
We're not the only drunk bums
there's strong points all across the world and all the mob is the epitome of it look at them
look at this bum i drink beer oh i go on a train i drink beer i piss on i piss i drink beer
i drink beer look at him with his stupid tonal beer
Alex Alex you sound so fucking salty man why you are so fucking salty Alex
Little bit
Don't you call it salty?
Yeah, don't you do that? You know, we can you chill a little bit man for your man. She please
Pick up the man. Hey, this is the English
Waking my heart
Not even by this time this is too late by tomorrow evening
Would
You both have orange hairs
Women's talking your dick and seeing orange pubic hairs. That's insane
Well, they log in. I'm a Latino, bro.
The pubic hairs are black.
Jeb black, yo, Ghibli, Jeb black
cubic hairs. No one wants to see
orange little nerdy orange hairs,
bro. By the way, did you hear?
Did you hear me?
Alexander gonna have a baby?
You are yeah
Well, you have a small cock Alex you sound like you are
Shut up show your stupid ponytail loser like I can see your shadow wheel dumb hair
This guy's a little fucking Frenchy hat on with a ponytail. He was a skirt. He's a drunk bum
Look at his drunk bum. Look at him. Look at his loser
Disgusting. Yeah, show that dick you drunk bum
haha you look at this loser his shadow says it all his shadow says it all bro yeah
hey i know i'm proud of it alex i'm proud of what i am no you're proud of being a drunk
loser bum with no wife and kids you don't have a family exactly you're walking around in daytime
drinking like a bum
That's insane
You showing a dirty tree and your beer and your dick, and you're proud of that
Watch doesn't fuck he bought that shit for 20 dollars in the fucking bodega
This is a bomb brother
You don't have a pot to piss and get that dirty watch out of my face brother that's them
Come to United States
This guy bought a fucking civil watch. It's already turning green
Look at your bum. It's American. It's a bomb. You know that right? You have no money
Yeah, yeah, okay run after them. Yeah, look at you, bro
Showing us
Berlin, I think this is
Nothing you have nothing I don't
I have exactly so shut the fuck up and keep showing it. Yeah, so what the fuck is your problem?
You're stupid dirty problem with graffiti piss piss again piss again, bro
This oh, this is a piece dude could you all you do is drink? He's gonna piss soon. Trust me on live panel again
He's gonna pull out his little fucking dick like signal 66 like he's doing right now
He has a beaker
Pissing on trees
shit whole town
With a way
Wake to hide your come on man
Obamov, I used to like you bro. So honestly
Boom loser
Yeah, that's what I am free. Yeah, get another beer get another beer alcoholic. You're an alcoholic bomb, brother
You wake up you sleep all day. You wake up and walk around like look. I'm a bomb. I'm gonna piss
Yeah, nice beer exactly
Alcohol, yeah
That's my life
What else are homeboy
What else they say they say tell us more
So you are you there Alex or what? What happened? Tell us more
Oh, what happened with Alex is he muted or what?
I can't hear you Alex. I'm sorry. You trust me psyche because I pawn bombed again tonight. I took Stephen King down
But anyways, Alexa, hopefully your periods will end, man
All I care is about impregnating Alexander Meyers and I'm a little chubby with her. Wham Wham, okay?
Since when do you like the
You believe that's okay, man. I'm on the list. I'm on the list brother. I'm a top contender. Yeah
Hey, you know, hey, you are on the fifth. You are the fiftieth man
Mayor's may have a baby and just going to the rainbow together and fuck all of you
The chair
Jesus I hope so too
You know the little baby, you gotta
Whatever if it doesn't work out she knows who to call
Yeah, okay, but anyways
Fuck you take that stupid handle
Well take the handle
Take it. Let the hair down. Let it out. Let the hair down. You have long hair. Oh, yeah, brother
You think I haven't seen it. Let it. Yes. Thank you. Let it out. Oh, you got a haircut. You got a haircut
Either that or the yeah, I'll be it's an opponent. Oh, I have a ponytail, but hey, have you seen the?
Boys from hell video
Gobble is from hell video. I have the same kind of hairstyle. I got my own
You're gonna come to New York over my like experience real life, I don't know what the fuck you're doing right now looking at
Like what is this?
Yep
This is crazy
What is it now?
Open them up, right on the sticker, right on the pole, put a sticker, who does that?
So you tell me there's losers that put stickers on light posts?
Look at that
Ah, unusually there are people
that's what you are afraid to go outside because you run your mouth
all the time
I'm fine finding you understand man. You catch on quick, bro
Yeah, look at it. Oh my god, come on over my piss. You got a piss
I know you do bro your old your liver's gone your kidneys you got a piss on my boy
You're holding it right now. You're holding in the piss right now. Just piss right there dick
Do it. Well, I your little dick
Yeah, look at your wrinkly hands your hands are wrinkly. Did you see his hands? There's wrinkles in the hand
This guy's 90 years old. We have a 90 year old freak
Yeah, look at his wrinkly hands. Look at that. There's rains
Look, that's oh my god. Is there a finger there? He's missing two fingers. He's missing fingers
He's got a fake gold watch on a beer. No fingers. He's got three fingers
Right. This is what we're dealing with. We got three finger boy
fake gold watch
Walking around. I don't know where the fuck he's walking around
Over my back to me this where the humans bro. Why are you the only one around?
Where is everybody?
Oh, yeah, exactly. Yeah, yeah, where everybody went. The whole city went quiet when you started out to talk.
Everybody's quiet when you talk.
Man, walk around Amsterdam, like alone, like what, where is everyone?
Look at this, there's no one in sight. How does this even, how does this town even work?
Like who runs this shit? You got to work and like produce. It's just like a ghost town of a drunk
Obamoff walking around pissing on whatever he pleases
This is a twilight zone episode from how
It looks nice. It looks like a nice town then it's so graffiti. It looks like garbage
There's one human here and there. How does this place even survive? Who is running this shit?
Who owns those cars?
What make who owns those stores? Is there any commerce going on any selling like you buy you sell you trade?
no
This is the empty streets
oblong mouth and
Empty streets
That's it. I don't get it. I don't get it. I don't I don't get it man
Can I please don't I pee online? Hey, Alex, can I pee on the street?
It seems like this whole town is your toilet. So just pee away my friend
away
Gracias
Look at his dick you have a big neck I can tell you you're rough you look at your rap
You have a long neck. Why do you have a jacket on you look fat with the jacket? You think I don't remember seeing you on naked
bro showing your cock
You have muscles so I don't know what you remember
I remember man. I remember when your little skirt with the wig and your cock flew out and you asking
Psyche if you can piss in a bucket like I remember
And now you're walking around here in an empty town
There's no humans rolling. Am I wrong look one human one human, bro. What the fuck is it?
this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this is this
I think it's a nightmare. I think I see cars. I see buildings being built, but I don't see humans. I don't see humans
Open up. Were you digging that hole and pissing it?
All it's a too big
Look at his dick
We're gonna run
Like a loser. He almost just fucking kidnapped a girl. You saw that he tried to grab her
That's crazy. What what?
Oh
Can you did you see her come out tall?
Maria did you see her come on? No, it's nice to me, man
Something's off here. I know it feels weird today. Okay. It's very weird. It's like the Truman show
Something's off here. I don't like it. I don't like it
It's weird
Me too. I don't like it
Oh, a human here and there with a dog. It doesn't make sense. Like, uh, hello
Not one human brother with a fucking this guy that humans don't exist besides a bench here and there like that's insane
this is not normal. Alex, I think you should write that is your retarded world work. I just don't
get it. Explain it to me all the time. It's Sunday. It's Sunday. It's holiday. Well, there's two
humans and the whole shit is just beautiful and trees. Look, there's no humans, bro. There's
no one around. I don't get it.
I don't give a fuck where on earth you are. This is not normal. Hey, that should be
There's no one around it's like you're in a movie set. It's literally it's like you're in a fucking movie set
With two extras walking around once in a while
This is yeah, I'm actually matching a matching the data you could go outside and have a beer outside
Not leaving in the fucking project. Yeah, you live in the fucking projects. Oh, yeah
Look at you with your wrinkly hands. Look at your dirty nails. You're just now. I know where the psyche gets it from you dirty nails
Fuck look at you
After them dirty nail motherfucker
Fake gold watch. Yo, take that piece of shit watch off and throw it away my man. That is the stupid
Brother, that's a five out of fake silver watch take it off and throw it away
No
I mix that's a five out of watch from a bodega
That's a file watch, bro
I
Think
This is crazy. There's bicycles everywhere. There's no humans. Who wants the bicycles? Why all these bikes there?
There's no one to ride them over the mouth. Who rides that shit?
Who parked that car like that? I see cars like you tell me some loser
Just parked that car and went into some abandoned building
This is like a ghost town. This doesn't make sense.
None of this makes sense at all, bro.
One car. Look at this shit.
One fucking car.
Doesn't make sense, my boy.
Okay.
A, U, Q, S, E, N, O, T, A, P, U, R.
Explain it, bro. I don't want it. I don't want to see shit. I want answers like look there's no one around no humans
There's no way it's just over mouth
There's no way
No, look one human one one just walked by him one where the fuck is this is loser
This guy's
This brother open up. You gotta forgive me. I live in New York. I step out of my house
There's five million people walking by me like I've never seen shit like this. What is this bro?
But we haven't seen you in the morning though. It's not like
It seems like it's morning and it should be humans going to breakfast and eating and shopping
Nobody nobody Ronys
Right look at this. No one you think it's a normal bro. What the fuck is this?
Where do you live?
No, hold on Germany or Amsterdam
Where are we? Oh, I think this is Spain. What is this fucking ghost town bullshit? What is this?
Yeah, this is Spain
Espana, yeah, this is crazy
P. Can you just pee for us? Please make us happy P
Yes, there's one that scooter. It's on something. There's no one around. You know, you're in trouble
You can literally piss on the hood of the car. Yeah, piss exactly jerk that cock
Piss my man. Yes, do it for
Look at him. We're stupid little black sneakers and his blue pants and red shirt from how
look at him
Oblamov
There's no one around dick. What the fuck am I looking at? Seriously? This is crazy
This is crazy, and it's not the first time over mouth every night you show your
Oh, yeah, we love the first time. Yeah alone
What is this? There's no humans. No cops. No traffic agents. No people going to school work
nothing
It's like the matrix like what the fuck is this shit? Where are the people, bro? I
See the buildings. I see the cars. Where are the people? Where are the people?
Where are they? I think they have a hangover. Where the fuck are the humans, brother?
And don't tell me when one loser walks by you like here. They are
One human and I have one car look just go by two hours one car
Look at this fucking
interview that
This is crazy
Anyway, I'm gonna be your sax and Joe mayors and that's it man. I may be over them off you can I
Would love to live there because I hate humans. So this is my fantasy. That's why I'm so
You know like going at you so hard bro. Where is this?
I need to move here. Oh, well, this is, uh, I would like to look around and I mean Barcelona. You understand me? Look at this. It's a ghost town. Not one human inside. I don't know how this place works. Explain yourself over the month. Explain it, man.
I can try
Look at all those windows and balconies. Yeah, pull that beer out dick now. He's gonna pee he's gonna pee on life
Look at that
So many buildings so many windows so many cars, but not one human around no babies no shoulders
You know no humans look at one human to like what the fuck is going on?
I'm not buying it open them up. I'm not buying him a man. You understand me?
Not buying it, brother.
Yeah, this is so calm in Europe.
On Sunday in Europe, it's like...
Fuck Europe. Europe sucks.
The United States take...
You know the only reason you're walking around like a loser right now is because of us. Okay. Remember that. Oh
You will not be
The United States
You're walking around like a loser in this piece of shit town
It's because of the United States of America homeboy. Don't ever forget that no one's protecting you right now
but us. This is why you're walking around like a fucking
this is what America is. Thank you, America.
No. Yeah. So keep walking around USA. So God dig.
The only reason you're walking around free right now like this with two humans
You look at that loser jog by you. It's because of the United States
Remember there's a
Where do you say USA run the shit you sermon and the story do you sell?
Because of us my boy
So what did you say?
And
Remember the United States of America runs the show and that's the only reason anybody in the planet is walking around safe
You understand me
Because we protect shit. And if you fuck up, we're gonna come down with blackhawks and fucking just rain hell on your head
So you stupid
Okay, it's not because of Germany it's not because the Netherlands it's because the United States of America
We run the planet. You understand Germany sucks our dick. Everybody sucks our dick
The only reason you're walking around open mouth like a drunk bomb right now in daytime because the USA made it happen for you homeboy
Remember that morning. It's morning. It's not daytime. Don't ever forget that brother. It's morning. It's morning
It's a ten o'clock. It's morning
It's not your drunk ass when you find out a watch. Thank you USA. Okay
And China because that's where you had to watch from ha ha ha this guy had a file watch or drunk like a bum
look at it
Look at him with his dirty sneakers his fucking stupid pants he had on yesterday
He came on ten times this motherfucker smells like shit. He hasn't even showered
He's been walking around for three days on live. Look at those sneakers. He found them in a dumpster
This guy look at his bum
This is wild
What a bum loser
New balance. He got new balance from a dumpster. That's his sneakers
But I'll watch I'm proud of it. I'm proud of it
With the Mariner watch that's worth $30,000. I were a watch
Dollar brother looking you a little five dollar time X
Go piss go piss again homeboy. Go piss go piss piss
Flat out the Timex
And he's got wires
You don't even have oh don't don't don't do that. Don't fucking reflection it up you bum. Look at you
Look at your bum ass in the reflection like a loser
As for any, keep walking with your fucking two dollar watches.
You're a bum, you're a drunk.
Look at that stupid hat.
He's posing look at his little leg. He put the leg up. He's posing. He doesn't give a fuck that he's a bum
He doesn't care this guy don't give a fuck
He'll walk around all day pissing and drinking all day long with a tool out watch and a stupid Frenchy
Have and his wrinkled three fucking finger hands and his fucking dumpster new bands sneakers all day every day
Yeah
Look at him look at him walk. So you got so you got shitpans
You got a fucking jacket. You got a little Frenchie. Hi, you have pony. I don't know what's happening right now, honestly
Well, he's a pig
He's looking for somewhere to piss
Look at him and he can't piss here because this is in public
He'll find a little dumpster alleyway to piss soon. Trust me
Look at him looking for piss. You got a pee, don't you?
Piss right there like a bum do it become you bro. Just be you piss in the middle street like a loser that you are
So you are the loser of this country I can tell
Off the bat. Yes, you're like everybody
People walking by you have a life like I gotta go to work or something you're just like I gotta drink and pee on psyche's panel
So you're a fucking loser bum
Go find some way to pee my boy
I can't find any place here
I know you can't
Okay, it's hard. Hey, man, you know, it's not easy
Chose your father watch again. Time X. What time is it?
Watch
Then watch
That's gold. Is that real gold? Oh my god, this guy's rich if that's gold. Yeah
this guy is a father of time
look at this, wow
I had a kindergarten
bro, I had that shit in kindergarten when I was playing around
like, wow
timex
timex from America
United States of America
he camped up with his frenchie hat
look at him, he's all pissed now
he's walking around all drunk
Don't get it man. Just don't get it
Yeah, Sylvia man, why are you have to understand something you know, it's a
Go pitch right now, bro. Good. Just just show us when you piss, bro. That's all I see. I want you to piss
Come on. Look at him. He's got a pee pee
Oh, he just poem bombed you psyche. That's poem bombing. That's naked pictures of women on the floor. Wow
Wow, I know that was an intentional but that could be considered poem bombing
Go fuck yourself man, but you just won't come to the channel. So
Go fuck yourself
On a sidewalk
You just bomb down this channel you piece of shit fuck you
You're such a bomb loser
You don't even realize that right like look at pictures of naked little girls
Let me like why would you even look at that brother? Did that turn you on did that turn you on?
Hmm you fucking bomb
Yeah, alcoholic bum, bro
With a wig
No, oh, yeah, you just formed on this child you moron no one this will fuck anymore what you have to show or say you understand
Oh, no, no Indian